A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #4749: Secrist and Kerrick (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - GP #4750: Miller and Steinberg (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - GP #4751: Cass and Dalmark (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - GP #4752: Brenda R. Eisenberg and Arieh Gilai (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - GP #4753: Iwazumi and Pollack (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - GP #4754: Josephson and Schwab (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - GP #4755: De Motta and Del Castillo (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - GP #4756: Takauji et.al. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - GP #4757: Masa Takuji, Masaaki Tsutsu-Ura and Torao Nagai (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - GP #4758: Vistor and Shapley (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - GP #4759: John M. Russell (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - GP #4760: Gotow et.al. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - GP #4761: Gotow et.al. (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - GP #4762: Gadsby and Cranefield (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - GP #4763: Huang, Catterall, etc. (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - GP #4764: Droogman's and Casteels (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - GP #4765: Michael Adler, Antonio C. Oliveira, Edson Albuquerque, Nabil A. Mansour and Amira T. Eldefrawi (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - GP #4766: Sheu and Fozzard (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - GP #4767: Morgan, Moss etc. (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - GP #4768: Anagnostopoulos (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - GP #4769: Richard A. Crocker, James Ringo, Myron L. Wolbarsht, and Henry G. Wagner (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - GP #4770: Yoshi, Kamo and Kurihara (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - GP #4771: Thellier, Hartmann (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - GP #4772: Balaban, Mandel etc. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - GP #4773: Robert D. Devoe and Rhonda S. Fine (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - GP #4774: Zamir et.al. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - GP #4775: Dragomir et.al. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - GP #4776: Samanen and Bernard (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - GP #4777: Edwards (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - GP #4778: Kilbridge and Ebrey (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - GP #4779: Michael P. Bohrer, William M. Deen, Channing R. Robertson, Julia L. Troy and Barry M. Brenner (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - GP #4780 ?Mullins and Requena (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - GP #4781: Eggena (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - GP #4782: Mulvany and Warshaw (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - GP #4783: Bennett and Lavidis (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - GP #4784: Shoukimad and French (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - GP #4785: Biedert, Barry and Smith (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - GP #4786: Clapham, Shrier (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - GP #4787: Yoram Grossman, Jeffrey A. Schmidt and Daniel L. Alkon (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - GP #4788: George McClellan and Saul Winegrad (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - GP #4789: Adolph and Kass (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - GP #4790: Saito, Kondo and Kato (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - GP #4791: Sorenson, Wood and Kirschner (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - GP #4792: Ahmed and Connor (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - GP #4793: Miller and Rosenberg (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - GP #4794: Pollack et.al. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - GP #4795: Violich and Requena (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - GP #4796: Strichartz, Oxford, etc. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - GP #4797: Hinke (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - GP #4798: M.L. Hernandez-Nicaise, G.O. Mackie and R.W. Meech (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - GP #4799: Joyner, Westerfield (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - GP #4800: Zecevic and Levitan (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - GP #4801: Shoei Yn Shiau and Wen-Mei Fu (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - GP #4802: Polimeni and Page (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - GP #4803: Nicholas A. Delamere, Christopher A. Paterson, George Duncan, and Douglas L. Holmes (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - GP #4804: T.M. Dwyer (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - GP #4805: T.M. Dwyer (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - GP #4806: Benos, Mandel and Simon (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - GP #4807: Kashiwagura, Kamo, Kurihara, Kobatake (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - GP #4808: Warner and Lachene (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - GP #4809: Kon, Maeda, etc. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - GP #4810: Arthur S. Polans, Joseph Hermolin and M. Deric Bownds (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - GP #4811: Daina Briedis, M.F. Moutrie and R.T. Balmer (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - GP #4812: Jerome F. Fiekers, Paul M. Spannbauer, Berthann Scubon- Mulieri and Rodney L. Parsons (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - GP #4813: Donald A. Farquharson (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - GP #4814: M.E. Clark and J.A.M. Hinke (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - GP #4815: M.E. Clark, J.A.M. Hinke and M.E. Todd (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - GP #4816: Kao, Yeoh, Goldfinger, Fuhrman and Mosher (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - GP #4817: Wilson (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - GP #4818: Richard M. Costanzo and Robert J. O?Connell (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - GP #4819: Joseph L. McArdle, Les Michelson, and Albert J. D?Alonzo (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - GP #4820: Roger Rick, Adolf Dorge, Uri Katz, Richard Bauer and Klaus Thurau (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - GP #4821: R.R. Warner and C. Lechene (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - GP #4822: Baruch, Minke and Kuno Kirschfeld (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - GP #4823: Pearson and Horowitz (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - GP #4824: Victor and Shapley (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - GP #4825: L.C. Stoner and F. M. Kregenow (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - GP #4826: Jerome F. Fiekers and Edward G. Henderson (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - GP #4827: Robert S. Stephenson and William L. Pak (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - GP #4828: Eli Orbach and Alan Finkelstein (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - GP #4829: Amy B. McDermott, Elizabeth A. Connor, Vincent E. Dionne and Rodney L. Parsons (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - GP #4830: Marion J. Siegman, Thomas M. Butler, Susan U. Mooers and Robert E. Davies (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - GP #4831: Ying Tung Lau and Robert H. Parsons (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - GP #4832: Hans Dieter Lux and Ger Hofmeir (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - GP #4832B: Lux and Hofmeier (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - GP #4832A: Lux and Hofmeier (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - GP #4833: Hans Dieter Lux and Gerd Hofmeier (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - GP #4834: Burks Oakley II, Dale G. Flaming and Kenneth T. Brown (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - GP #4835: Deric Bownds and Michael S. Biernbaum (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - GP #4836: Henry A. Lester, Mauri E. Krouse, Menasche M. Nass, Norbert H. Wasserman and Bernard F. Erlanger (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - GP #4837: B.J. Starkey (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - GP #4838: Guy Salama, Robert G. Johnson and Antonio Scarpa (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - GP #4839: Dorrscheidt- Kafer (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - GP #4840: John W. Krueger, Damian Forletti and Beatrice A. Wittenberg (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - GP #4841: Chester J. Karwoski and Luis M. Proenza (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - GP #4842: Jack A. Rall (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - GP #4843: C.M. Armstrong and W. F. Gilly (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - GP #4844: W. Almers and C.M. Armstrong (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - GP #4845: Mope, McCLellan and Winegrad (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - GP #4846: McClellan and Winegrad (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - GP #4847: Arthur M. Brown, Syozo Yasui and Norio Akaike (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - GP #4848: C.M. Tang, G.R. Srichartz and R.K. Orkand (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - GP #4849: A.S. Verkman and A.K. Solomon (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - GP #4850: C.R. Scheid and F.S. Fay (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - GP #4851- third revision: E.M. Landau, B. Gavish, D.A. Nachshen (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - GP #4852: Stephen Gluck and Qais Al-Awqati (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - GP #4853: Timothy J. Hill and Tishar K. Chowdhury (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - GP #4854: Tomiyuki Hara and Reiko Hara (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - GP #4855: L.J. Mullins (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - GP #4856: Isao Inoue (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - GP #4857: Luis Reuss, Steven A. Weinman and Timothy P. Grady (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - GP #4858: N. Daskal, E.M. Landau and Y. Lass (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - GP #4859: Lisa Ebihara, Norikazu Shigeto, Melvyn Lieberman, Edward A. Johnson (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - GP #4860: Ken Takeda, Peter H. Barry and Peter W. Gage (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - GP #4861: Alfred Strickholm (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - GP #4862: Flemming, Cornelius (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - GP #4863: Samuel S. Wong and Kenneth L. Dretchen (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - GP #4864: Douglas C. Eaton and Malcolm S. Brodwick (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - GP #4865: Barry S. Palotta and George D. Webb (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - GP #4866: Shey-Shing Sheu, Michael Korth, David A. Lathrop and Harry Fozzard (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - GP #4867: C.Caputo and R. DiPolo (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - GP #4868: Donald M. Bers, Kenneth D. Philipson and Glenn A. Langer (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - GP #4869: Mark T. Nelson and Mordecai P. Blaustein (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - GP #4870: R.T. Mathias, R.A. Levis and R.S. Eisenberg (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - GP #4871: Daisuke Yammamoto, Jun-ichi Fukami and Hiroshi Washio (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - GP #4872: Daisuke Yamamoto and Hiroshi Washio (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - GP #4873: Gregory M. Fahy (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - GP #4874: Michael E. Pine, Wesley W. Brooks, John J. Nosta and Walter M. Abelmann (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - GP #4875: R.S. Kass and M. L. Blair (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - GP #4876: Paul Kilbride (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - GP #4877: John H.B. Bridge, Glenn A. Langer and William r. Cabeen Jr. 10/8/79 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - GP #4878: Dunham, Tucker, Simonsen and Ellroy 10/10/79 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - GP #4879: Joshua Zimmerberg, Fredric S. Cohen and Alan Finkelstein (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - GP #4880: Frederic S. Cohen, Joshua Zimmerberg and Alan Finkelstein (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - GP #4881: Mei-Ven C. Lo and William L. Pak (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - GP #4882: W.T. Clusin (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - GP #4883: W.T. Clusin (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - GP #4884: C.R.J. Greenleaf (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - GP #4885: Fisher, Erlij, and Helman (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - GP #4886: J.M. Salhany (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - GP #4887: Richard Horn and Malcolm S. Brodwick (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - GP #4888: Peter Cala (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - GP #4889: Dwyer, Adams and Hille (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - GP #4890: Adams, Dwyer and Hille (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - GP #4891: Naylor and Elliott (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - GP #4892: Rodland and Dunham, 1979 November 5 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - GP #4893: F. Ramon (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - GP #4894: G. Droogman?s and R. Casteels, Ronald W. Ral (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - GP #4895: Edwards, Ottoson, Rydqvist and Swerup (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - GP #4896: Javier Narvarte and Arthur L. Finn (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - GP #4897: Hinke, White and Chow (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - GP #4898: J.E. Stengel and K.L. Magelby (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - GP #4899: Bruce K. Krueger, Ronald W. Ratzlaff and Mordecai P. Blaustein (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - GP #4900: Samuel Litwin (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - GP #4901: Abraham B. Eastwood, Clara Franzine-Armstrong and Camillo Peracchia (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - GP #4902: Ichiro Shimada and Teiichi Tanimura (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - GP #4903: Ete Z. Szuts (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - GP #4904: Zidek, Speckman and Lehmenkuhler (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - GP #4905: Angela M. Hyman and Marion E. Frank (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - GP #4906: Angela M. Hyman and Marion Frank (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - GP #4907: Kim, They and Lauf (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - GP #4908: Zengel, Magleby, Horn, mcAfee and Yarowsky (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - GP #4909: Robert M. Gunn and Otto Frolich (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - GP #4910: begenisich and Deweer (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - GP #4911: Ananda Weerasuriya, Robert A. Spangler, Stanley I. Rapoport and Robert A. Taylor (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - GP #4912: G.E. Kirsch, J. Z. Yeh, J.M. Farley and T. Narahashi (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - GP #4913: David Landowne and V. Scruggs (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - GP #4914: Richard P. Kline, Harris Ripps and John E. Dowling (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - GP #4915: R.A. Sjodin (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - GP #4916: J.E. Lisman, S. Schulman, Y. Sheline and P.K. Brown (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - GP #4917: Douglas C. Eaton (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - GP #4918: M.A. Pahlavani (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - GP #4919: T.C. Terwilliger and A.K. Solomon (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - GP #4920: Jerry M. Farley, Shigenori Watanabe, Jay Z. Yeh and Toshio Narahashi (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - GP #4921: Michael A. Lang (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - GP #4922: Rhoda Blostein, Pierre Drapeau and Stephen Benderoff (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - GP #4923: Pedro Labarca, Robert Coronado and Christopher Miller (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - GP #4924: Roberto Coronado, Robert L. Rosenberg and Christopher Miller (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - GP #4925: Loren H. Cohen and Philip R. Steinmetz (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - GP #4926: Dennis s. Miura, Stefan Biedert and William H. Barry (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - GP #4927: Philip R. Steinmetz, Russell F. Husted, Allan Mueller and Renaud Beauwens (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - GP #4928: Jagdish Gulati and Richard J. Podolsky (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - GP #4929: Michael W. Levine and Jeremy M. Shefner (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - GP #4930: R. H. Gandy and D. M. Matthews (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - GP #4931: F. Llados, D.R. Matteson and M.E. Kriebel (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - GP #4932: A.S. Verkman, James A. Dix, L.C. Cantley and A.K. Solomon (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - GP #4933: Jose Negreiros and Luis Alberto A. Silva (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - GP #4934: Ronald F. Abercrombie, Leona M. Masukawa, Raymond A. Sjodin and David Livengood (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - GP #4935: Phyllis R. Robinson, Satoru Kawamura, Bruce Abramson and M. Deric Bownds (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - GP #4936: Robert S. Zucker (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - GP #4937: K.N. Leibovic (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - GP #4938: Kenjiro Izumi, Tatsumi Ito and Toshiyuki Fukazuma (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - GP #4939: Haruyasu Furukawa, John P. Bilezikian and John N. Loeb (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - GP #4940: Jeremy J. Lambert, Nicholas N. Durant, Robert L. Volle and Edward G. Henderson (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - GP #4941: J. Francis Heidlage and Allan W. Jones (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - GP #4942: J. Francis Heidlage and A.W. Jones (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - GP #4943: Charles F. Meier, Jr. and Bertram G. Katzung (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - GP #4944: C.J. Karwoski and L.M. Proenza (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - GP #4945: U. Till, H. Petermann, I. Wenz and P. Arese (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - GP #4946: P. Arese, A. Bosia, G.P. Pescarmona and U. Till (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - GP #4947: R. Ugor Gamow and Barbel Bottger (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - GP #4948: Muriel H. Nathan and Sarah S. Winans (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - GP #4949: D.A. Nachshen and M.P.Blaustein (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - GP #4950: David W. Maughan and Robert E. Godt (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - GP #4951: Klaus-Jaochim Schott (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - GP #4952: Shigehiro Nakajima and Arieh Gilai (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - GP #4953: Shigehiro Nakajima and Arieh Gilai (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - GP #4954: Joel Linden and Gary Brooker (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - GP #4955: Gerry S. Oxford (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - GP #4956: Charles Tanford (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - GP #4957: Luis Monti-Bloch and H. Mack Brown (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - GP #4958: H. Mack Brown and Luis Monti-Bloch (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - GP #4959: D.C. Spray, A.L. Harris and M.V.L. Bennett (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - GP #4960: A. L. Harris, D.C. Spray and M.V.L. Bennett (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - GP #4961: Stuart B. Barton and Ira S. Cohen (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - GP #4962: Kiyonori Yoshii, Yonosuke Kobatake and Kenzo Kurihara (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - GP #4963: Herbert S. Chase Jr. and Qais Al-Awqati (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - GP #4964: Adolph I. Cohen (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - GP #4965: Richard A. Weiss (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - GP #4966: Li-Yen Mae Huang and Gerald Ehrenstein (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - GP #4967: M. H. Friedman and R.A. Meyer (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - GP #4968: Hideyo Kuroda and Ritsu Kuroda (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - GP #4969: Julius J. Friedman, and Norina E. DeRose (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - GP #4970: Juan I. Korenbrot and San-Bao Hwang (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - GP #4971: J. Requena and L. Mullins (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - GP #4972: Elizabeth W. Stephenson (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - GP #4973: Charles M. Wormington (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - GP #4974: Bruce P. Bean, Peter Shrager and David A. Goldstein (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - GP #4975: Cherem, Rodrigues and Klahr (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - GP #4976: Hermann and Gorman (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - GP #4977: Hermann and Gorman (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - GP #4978: W. Glenn L. Kerrick, Phyllis E. Hoar, P.S. Cassidy and Dean A. Malencik (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - GP #4979: J. Aubineau, G. Haudecoeur and P. Guilbault (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - GP #4980: Jacky Aubineau and Pierre Guilbault (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - GP #4981: Barry S. Winkler (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - GP #4982: William Van Der Kloot and Hiroshi Kita (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - GP #4983: R. DiPolo and L.Beauge (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - GP #4984: H. Ripps, L. Mehaff III, M. Siegal, W. Ernst (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - GP #4985: Harris Ripps, Leathem Mehaffey III and Irwin M. Siegal (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - GP #4986: Harris Ripps, Leathem Mehaffey III and Irwin M. Siegal (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - GP #4987: Didier Garnier, Joel Nargeo and Oger Rougier (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - GP #4988: Stuart McLaughlin, Nancy Mulrine, Thomas Gresalfi, Gerard Vaio and Alan McLaughlin (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - GP #4989: Stuart McLaughlin and Joel Brown (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - GP #4990: Arthur S. Polans, Satoru Kawamura and M. Deric Bownds (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - GP #4991: J. Walter Woodbury and David D. Busath (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - GP #4992: Christiane Crone and Ove Christensen (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - GP #4993: G.J.M.Stienen and T. Blange (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - GP #4994: Isao Inoue (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - GP #4995: Robert M. Champman, John W. McCrary and John R. Tuttle (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - GP #4996: Randophe P. Swenson Jr. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - GP #4997: Gary Strichartz and Christina Hansen Bay (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - GP #4998: A.Y. Nassar, M.K. Salah and Abd Allah (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - GP #4999: Hiroshi Nikaido and Emiko Y. Rosenberg (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - GP #5000: Jorge Fischbarg, Jonn J. Lim and Sheila R. Fischer (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - GP #5001: Satoru Kawamura and M. Deric Bownds (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - GP #5002: Mads Dalmark and Hans H. Storm (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - GP #5003: Josef Skrzypek and Frank S. Werblin 8/14/80 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - GP #5004: Hikaru Suzuki and Hiroshi Kuriyama (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - GP #5005: L.C. Fritz and A. Mauro (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - GP #5006: Ramon Latorre, James J. Donovan, Walter Koroshetz, Daniel C. Tosteson and Balthasar F. Gisin (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - GP #5007: J.E. Zengel and K.L. Magleby (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - GP #5008: Makoto Kashiwayanagi, Kiyonori Yoshii, Yonosuke Kobatake and Kenzo Kurihara (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - GP #5009: P. Pennefather and D.M.J. Quastel (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - GP #5010: Vincent G. Dethier and Robert Crnjar (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - GP #5011: M. Anderson (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - GP #5012: Ximena Cecchi, Osvaldo Alvarez, and Ramon Latorre (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - GP #5013: M. Tsacopoulos, S. Poitry and A. Brosellino (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - GP #5014: M. Zamir (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - GP #5015: Fumio Kukita and Shunichi Yamagishi (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - GP #5016: Jun Asayama, Lincoln E. Ford and Mary F. Surdyk-Droske (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - GP #5017: Stephen R. Bolsover (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - GP #5018: Meegan J. Wilson, and Sanford E. Ostroy (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - GP #5019: M.A. Milanick and R.B. Gunn (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - GP #5020: L.J. Mullins and J. Requena (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - GP #5021: Charles J. Cohen, Bruce P. Bean, Thomas J. Colatsky and Richard W. Tsien (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - GP #5022: Duane R. Edgington and Ann E. Stuart (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - GP #5023: Julian Borejdo, Olga Assulin and Rena Yarom (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - GP #5024: Fulton Wong, Bruce W. Knight and Frederick A. Dodge (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - GP #5025: Ted Begenisich and David Busath (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - GP #5026: John R. Clay and Alvin Shrie (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - GP #5027: Richard Hahin and Gary Strichartz (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - GP #5028: R.B. Stein and F. Parmiggiani (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - GP #5029: F. Parmiggiani and R.B. Stein (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - GP #5030: F. Parmiggiani, R.B. Stein and R. Rolf (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - GP #5031: Pedro U.I. Salas and Julio H. Moreno (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - GP #5032: Michael Cahalan and James Hall (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - GP #5033: James E. Hall and Michael Callahan (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - GP #5034: John M. Russell and Malcolm S. Brodwick (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - GP #5035: Robert U. Muller and Gary Orin and Charles S. Peskin (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - GP #5036: Robert U. Muller and Charles S. Peskin (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - GP #5037: Michael Crow and Martin J. Kushmerick (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - GP #5038: J. R. Hume and W. Giles (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - GP #5039: James C. Boudreau, Joseph J. Oravec and Nga Kieu Hoang (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - GP #5040: Richard J. Paul (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - GP #5041: John C. Parker (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - GP #5042: Margaret R. Clark, John C. Guatelli, Anthony T. White and Stephen B. Shohet (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - GP #5043: Jurgen F. Fohlmeister and William J. Adelman (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - GP #5044: M.R. Bennett and N.A. Lavidis (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - GP #5045: D.R. Davey and M.R. Bennett, 1980 December 29 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - GP #5046: Thomas F. Sherman (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - GP #5047: W.J. Culp (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - GP #5048: Robert D. Prusch (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - GP #5049: Alexandre Fabiato (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - GP #5050: Samuel Cukierman and Antonio Paes de Carvalho, 1981 January 21 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - GP #5051: Samuel Cukierman and Antonio Paes de Carvalho (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - GP #5052: E.F. Nemeth and W.W. Douglas (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - GP #5053: Gordon A. Plishker (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - GP #5054: Gordon A. Plishker and Patsy H. White (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - GP #5055: Ira Josephson and Nick Sperelakis (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - GP #5056: J.A. Heiny, J.R. Valle, and S.H. Bryant (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - GP #5057: Leona M. Masukawa and David R. Livengood (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - GP #5058: Reinaldo DiPolo and Luis Beauge (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - GP #5059: Emil Bozler (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - GP #5060: Michael M. White and Christopher Miller (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - GP #5061: Robert W. Mercer and Philip B. Dunham (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - GP #5062: Dennis C. Larrivee, Sherry K. Conrad, Robert S. Stephenson and William L. Pak (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - GP #5063: Edward D. Lipson and Steven M. Block (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - GP #5064: Jonas B. Galper, Louise C. Dziekan, Dennis S. Miura and Thomas W. Smith (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - GP #5065: Baruch Minke (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - GP #5066: Stanley I. Rapoport, Veronica Nassar-Gentina and Janet V. Passonneau (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - GP #5067: J.J. Nordmann, J.P. Desmazes and D. Georgescauld (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - GP #5068: Bo-Eric Persson and Kenneth R. Spring (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - GP #5069: Mitzy Canessa, Isabel Bize, Norma Adragna, and Daniel Tosteson (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - GP #5070: Ronald S. Aronson, Edmund C.H. Keung and Chi Sing Keung (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - GP #5071: E.M. Tucker, C.E. Smalley, J.C. Ellory and P.B. Dunham (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - GP #5072: Donald E. Brooks and Russell G. Grieg, 1981 March 31 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - GP #5073: Russell C. Grieg and Donald E. Brooks (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - GP #5074: Roger Herriott (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - GP #5075: Kenneth A. Rubinson, 1981 April 2 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - GP #5076: Kent M. Chapman, 1981 April 9 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - GP #5077: Robert E. Godt and Barry D. Lindley (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - GP #5078: Francisco Bezanilla, Robert E. Taylor and Julio M. Fernandez (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - GP #5079: Julio M. Fernandez, Francisco Bezanilla and Robert E. Taylor (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - GP #5080: Joel Nargeot, Henry A. Lester, Nigell J.M. Birdsall, Jane Stockton, Norbert H.Wasserman and Bernard F. Erlanger (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - GP #5081: D.R. Matteson and C.M. Armstrong, 1981 April 20 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - GP #5082: Herbert L. Meltzer and Alice Holtz (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - GP #5083: H. Parnas, J. Dudel and I. Parnas, 1981 April 27 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - GP #5084: J.O. Wieth and P.J. Bjerrum, 1981 April 28 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - GP #5085: Fleming Cornelius (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - GP #5088: K.A.P.Edman, G. Elzinga and M.I.M. Noble (Box 83, Folder 17)